loquax.co.uk 2019-11-08

# Loquax Privacy Policy

**General policy**   
Loquax respects your privacy. The information that you provide us with, or that is gathered automatically helps us and third parties to monitor our service and provide you with the services that you have subscribed to. Please bear in mind that any personal information that you submit through forums, letters/emails for publication and the like may be collected by others. In accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation we have expanded our privacy policy to include a list of what personal data we collect, why we collect it and who, if anyone, we share it with. You can read that document here. If you have any concerns, questions or comments please email [comps@loquax.com](mailto:comps@loquax.com?Subject=Privacy)

**Email newsletters**   
Loquax operates email newsletters on its site. These are free to sign up to. What we ask of you is your email address, at times we may ask you for further information, which is used for demographic purposes. We do not give our email lists out to other parties. Our newsletters may contain promotions or advertisements from various businesses or information on other sites or services that we offer. If at any time you wish to unsubscribe from our newsletter you may do so by visiting the site you signed up with and using the unsubscribe facility. You may also email the site admin although it may take a longer time before your email address is removed than with the automatic unsubscribe facility. 

**Registration**   
Our site may require you to register with us. This is to allow access to extra services that we provide for you. The information is not used for sending you newsletters or promotions unless stated. 

**Third party sites**   
Our site operates with third party sites (such as online shops and gaming sites). They will have their own terms and privacy conditions and you're advised to check with them. 

**Cookies**   
We use 'cookies' in order to be able to offer user tools such as the tracker and forums. With some links out of Loquax, namely affiliate links (see below), you may get third party cookies for other purposes such as order tracking in online shops or for targeting advertisements to particular types of visitor. You can find out more about our [cookies policy](https://www.loquax.co.uk/cookies.htm). 

**Affiliate Marketing**   
In some instances we use affiliate links to generate income for Loquax. These links earn us commission based on sales or other user activity. We most likely don't get paid per click. Affiliate links can mainly be found in the offers and gaming sections of the site. Some competition listings, usually the top sites in each listing prior to a full A-Z list, will have an affiliate link. These have no effect on you or our editorial decisions and content. In the main, most competition links are not affiliate links. 

**Surveys**   
On occasion we may conduct online surveys. This is used to gauge our service, collect demographic information and other information that we may find useful. These surveys are optional. 

**Security**   
While we strive to keep the information that you supply directly or indirectly secure please be aware that the Internet is not a fully secure medium. 

**Competitions**   
From time to time we operate competitions and promotions. Participation in these is optional. Information submitted may be submitted to third party sponsors so do check individual competition rules. You may also be given an option to sign up for a free email newsletter, opting out of this does not disqualify you from a competition. 

**Usage of information**   
If requested we may submit your information to local or government authorities. 

**Corrections/updates**   
You may unsubscribe from our newsletters using the facilities available on the website you signed up with or by emailing the relevant online editor. If you have any problems please email [comps@loquax.com](mailto:comps@loquax.com)

**Policy Changes**   
By using our site you agree to accept this privacy policy and are aware that our policy may change with time. Any changes to this policy will appear on this web page.
